怎么了
What's going on?
我的眼睛有点痒
Well, my eye is a little itchy.
我的也是
Uhhh, mine too! Yeah.
你的眼睛好红
Wow! It's really red!
你应该去看我的眼科医生
You should go see my eye doctor.
理查德  我才不要找你的前男友看眼睛
Richard? I'm not gonna go see your ex-boyfriend!
理查德  一天到晚理查德个没完
Oh, Richard. That's all I ever hear, Richard, Richard, Richard!
我们约会以后  我只提过两次他的名字
Since we've been going out, I think I've mentioned his name twice!
那好  理查德  理查德
Okay, so Richard, Richard!
不是理查德  我新找的眼科医生很棒
It's not Richard! Okay? It's this new guy and he's really good.
抱歉  我不去看眼科医生
Well, I'm sorry I'm not going to an eye doctor!
天啊  老毛病又犯了
Oh God, here we go!
什么
What?
只要是碰她的眼睛
Anytime anything comes close to touching her eye
或是别人碰自己眼睛  她就会害怕  看
or anyone else's she like freaks out. Watch! Watch!
罗斯  你别闹了
Ross! Come on! That's all right!
好的  我对我的眼睛有怪癖
Fine--Okay, I have a weird thing about my eye.
-麻烦别再讨论了  行吗  -好的
- Can we not talk about it please? - All right, fine.
瑞秋  还记得那首很棒的歌吗
Hey Rach, remember that great song,
"本人  自己和我"(I与eye同音)
Me, Myself, and I?
莫妮卡  别闹啦
Monica! Come on!
有没有人想吃午餐  有愿意的请说我
Hey, does anybody want to get some lunch? All those in favor say I?
罗斯  拜托别闹了啦
Ross! Stop it! Come on!
我好喜欢看《国王与我》
How much did I love The King and I?
钱德勒
Chandler!
我也是
Me too! Me too! Me too!
够了  别玩了
Just stop it! Come on!
你还好吧
You okay there man?
我真的戳到了
Yeah, I got too excited!
先走了  我要带本去公园
All right, I gotta go. I'm taking Ben to the park.
帮我亲一下他
Ohh, give him a kiss for me!
好  再见
All right, bye!
再见
Bye!
回见
Later!
很抱歉让你们夹在中间尴尬
I am so sorry you got caught in the middle of that.
我也不是故意这么夸张
I didn't mean to be so out there.
但我真的很生他的气
I am furious with him!
别激动
Wow umm, calm down.
我在克制  但一想到那个人我就有气
I'm trying, but man that guy can push my buttons!
你干嘛那么气他
Why are you so mad at him?
我不想谈  好吗
Look, I don't wanna talk about it. Okay?
只是
Well, it just seems that...
你想榜上有名  就继续说啊
You wanna be on my list too? Keep talking!
对了  谁有看到我的黑名单
Has anyone seem my list by the way?
没看到  菲比  长什么样子
Uh, no Pheebs. What's it look like?
就是张纸  上头写了"罗斯"
Uh, it's a piece of paper and it says, "Ross" on it.
了解
I see.
我刚和艾丝特尔讲完电话  你们猜怎么着
I just got off the phone with Estelle and guess what.
我要当电影主角了
I got the lead in a movie!
你要当电影主角  太厉害了
You got the lead in a movie? That's amazing!
是什么电影
What's the movie about?!
片名是《快门速度》  超酷的
It's called Shutter Speed, it's really cool!
我在地铁遇见一个女孩
Yeah, umm, I meet this girl in the subway
一天之内坠入情网
and we fall in love in like a day, right?
后来她消失无踪
And then, she disappears...
但我找到了她的住处  去了后
But I find out where she lives and when I get there
一个老太太出来开门  我问她
this like old lady answers the door and I say,
"贝丝在哪里"
"Where's Betsy?" Right?
她说"贝丝已经过世十年了"
And she says, "Betsy's been dead for 10 years."
好恐怖哦
Ohh-oh, chilling!
最棒的是  拍片地点在赌城外的沙漠
And the best part is, we're filming in the desert outside Vegas!
兄弟  你知道这意味着什么
And you know what that means buddy!
兄弟  我知道这意味着什么
Yeah, I know that means buddy!
开车杀过去  我们可以租辆车
Road trip! Yeah, we can rent a car!
我周二以前到那里就行了
I just have to be there by Tuesday!
等等  我外婆过世了
Oh wait, my grandmother's dead.
菲比  我们也可以聊聊那件事
Well, uh, we can talk about that too Pheebs.
不  我是说她的计程车
No! No, her cab!
她八成用不到了  你们可以开去赌城
She probably won't be using it; you can drive it to Las Vegas.
好耶  菲比  谢了
All right! Thanks Pheebs!
等等  那我的工作怎么办
Whoa-whoa-whoa, what are we going to do about my job?
别去了
Oh umm, not go.
好耶  棒  公路旅行
All right, great, road trip baby!
你没意见吧
This okay with you?
钱德勒  你不用征求我的允许
Chandler! You don't have to ask for my permission.
我让你去
You can go.
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋  快点  要去看眼科了
Hey Rach, come on! We're gonna be late for the eye doctor appointment!
好啦  早去早解脱
All right! Let's get this over with!
糟糕  我真是笨手笨脚的
No! Look what I did!
搞得一团乱
Oh, I mean, look at this mess!
我们得先来清理一下
I mean, we're probably gonna have to clean this up! Y'know?
看病时间得要重约了
We're gonna have to reschedule!
若你认为这点脏乱就会影响我
If you thought this mess is going to bother me,
那你就错了
you are wrong!
我们走吧  眨眼姑娘
All right, let's go Blinky!
钱德勒
Chandler!!!!
乔伊  你怎么了
Oh hey Joey! What's up?
我无法决定走哪条路去赌城
I can't decide which route to take to Vegas.
你去过不少地方吧
Hey, you've traveled a lot right?
对  见过世面
Yeah, I've been around.
那我该选哪一条路
Okay, so-so which route should I take
北线还是南线
the northern route or the southern route?
走北线经伊利诺斯州
Ooh, if you take the northern route
有个男人用蜜蜂当胡子
there's a man in Illinois with a beard of bees.
太棒了  问题解决
Great! Problem solved!
但是走南线的话  可以看会玩井字棋的鸡
But on the southern route there's a chicken that plays tic-tac-toe.
又回到原点了
Well, back to square one.
我知道有个方法能让你做决定
Oh, I know a way that you can decide!
我会问你一连串的问题
All right, I'm going to ask you a series of questions
你回答得越快越好
and you answer as quickly as you can.
好
Yes!
很好  不过先别急
Good, but wait.
开始吧
Okay, all right, here we go.
你先放轻松
Now I want you to relax.
深呼吸  心里不要想事情
Take a deep breath. Clear your mind.
花生酱和蛋白  你喜欢哪个
Which do you like better peanut butter or egg whites?
花生酱
Peanut butter!
你想当什么  消防员还是游泳选手
Which would you rather be a fireman or a swimmer?
游泳选手
A swimmer!
你想和谁上床  莫妮卡还是瑞秋
Who would you rather sleep with Monica or Rachel?
莫妮卡
Monica. Oh...
我一直都以为是瑞秋呢
huh, I always thought it would be Rachel.
不要想事情  细领带还是宽领带
No thinking! No thinking! Tie or ascot?
宽领带
Ascot!
北线还是南线
North route or south route?
北线
North route!
答案出现  厉害吧
Bamn! There you go! Huh?
不可思议
Wow! That was incredible!
蜜蜂胡  我来啦
Beard of bees, here I come!
这家伙又来了
Oh, this guy again.
还好吗
Hey man, what's up?
普通  今晚想看电影吗
Uhh, not much. You guys want to see a movie tonight?
好啊  你要看什么
Sure, what do you want to see?
不知道
I don't know, umm...
我知道要如何决定
Oh, I know how we can decide.
菲比  让他见识下你的游戏
Phoebe, show him your game!
免了  多谢
Umm, no thank you.
她是怎么了
What's with her?
不知道
I don't know.
但我知道怎么决定
But hey, I know we can decide.
我问你问题  你要很快回答
Okay, I'm gonna ask you questions and you answer real quick. Okay?
好
Okay.
你喜欢哪种  动作片还是喜剧
What do you like better action or comedy?
动作片
Action.
你想跟谁上床  莫妮卡还是瑞秋
Who would you rather sleep with Monica or Rachel?
老兄  你真变态
Dude, you are sick.
抱歉  我忘了你和瑞秋的陈年旧账了
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot you had that whole Rachel thing.
天啊  这是干嘛的
Oh my God! What does that thing do?
这是眼球摘除机
Oh that's an eye removal machine.
好了  我要走了
All right, I'm outta here!
开玩笑的啦
I'm kidding! I'm kidding!
瑞秋
Hi Rachel!
我是米勒医生
I'm Dr. Miller.
莫妮卡说你有点紧张
Monica told me you were a little nervous,
不过别担心  不会有事的
but don't worry everything's gonna be just fine.
那就结束吧
So were done then!
-还差一点  我们要先开始  -好的
- Almost! But first, we gotta start. - Okay.
这是青光眼检查仪
This is a glaucoma test.
请坐
Sit down.
好吧
Okay.
把下巴放在这里
But your chin here.
眼睛会有点风吹的感觉
Now, you'll feel a small puff of air in each eye.
什么
What?!
一点点的风  你快点
A small puff of air, now come on!
开始了
Here we go.
好
All right.
一  二  三
1...2...3!
抱歉  好吧  我这次不会动
I'm sorry. All right, I'll just stay in here this time. Okay.
好了吗
Ready?
一  二
1...2...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我来按住她的头好了
Y'know what, I'm gonna hold her head.
不用了
That's okay.
好吧
Okay.
一  二
1...2!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你还年轻  应该没有青光眼
Y'know what? You're young; you probably don't have glaucoma.
太好了  很高兴认识你
Great!! It was very, very nice to meet you sir--
你在干嘛  你疯了不成
Ow! Hey! What are you doing?! Are you crazy!
没事  你的左眼有些轻微感染
Okay. You've got a small, minor infection in that left eye.
这眼药水一天点三次连续一周
I want you to take these drops three times a day for a week
你就会痊愈了
and you'll be as good as new.
我不会把任何东西放进眼睛里
Yeah, no, I don't-I don't put things in my eye.
那好吧  三个月后再见
Okay then, I guess we'll see you back here in three months.
-好的  -我到时帮你装上假眼
- Great! - And I'll fit you for a glass eye.
好啦  把那破眼药水给我
Okay, just give me the damn drops!
米勒医生  PECFD
Dr. Miller? P E C F D.
莫妮卡  棒极了
Very good Monica!
你知道奖品放在哪里
You know where they are.
我当然知道
I sure do!
你没有
And you don't get one!
我得说  那眼药水实在是太神奇了
Y'know, I-I gotta tell ya, those eye drops are a miracle.
我的眼睛百分之百好了
My eye is a 100% better.
眼药水还放在我的外套里
They're still in my coat.
可恶
Damn!
准备好上路了没
Hey! You ready to go?
好了  不过那边会有多冷
Yeah, listen, how cold is it going to be there?
我要带外套  还是这些毛衣背心就够了
Do I need a coat or will all these sweater vests be enough?
怎么了
What?
我爱你
I love you.
真希望罗斯也能一起去
Man, I wish Ross was coming with us!
我一定会很想念他的
Y'know? I'm gonna miss him!
真是多谢你了  我才刚把那个混蛋给忘掉
Thanks a lot! I just got that jerk out of my mind!
我们住哪里
Hey, so where are we staying?
电影公司招待的饭店大套房吗
Is the movie putting us up in a big hotel suite?
不是  这是独立制片的电影
Uh no, not really. It's an independent film y'know?
没有大预算
So we don't have a real big budget.
我想我就住你房间好了
I figured I'd just stay in your room.
了解  但等你拿到片酬之后
I see, but once you get your first paycheck
你就有饭店大套房住了  对吗
you'll be springing a big hotel suite, right?
主演电影的片酬一定不少吧
I mean, lead in a movie, they must be paying you a lot?
是啊  我算给你听
Oh yeah! Check this out.
《快门速度》每赚一块钱
For every dollar Shutter Speed makes,
就有一分落入乔伊的腰包
one penny of it goes right in Joey's pocket.
所以电影赚钱你才有钱拿
So you don't get paid unless the movie makes money?
你不知道这电影的情节吗
Did you not hear the plot of the movie?
"她已经过世十年了"
"She's been dead for ten years."
我就快变成百万富翁了
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
我只是来跟你们说个再见
I just wanna say good-bye to you guys
顺便托你们帮我下个注
and to see if you guys will place a little bet for me, huh?
二十块押黑色15号
Twenty bucks on black 15.
没问题
You got it!
好
All right!
再见了
All right, bye-bye now!
再见
Bye you guys!
我送你上车
I wanna say good-bye at the car!
好
Okay!
谁要送我上车的
Anybody want to say good-bye to me at the car?
亲爱的  我愿意送你上车
Oh honey, I'll say good-bye to you at the car
只要你不介意我眼睛化脓了
if you don't mind the puss.
再见
See ya!
等等  化脓是好现象
Well, wait a minute! The puss is good!
表示快要好了
It means it's healing!
菲比  你在看什么
Hey Pheebs, what'cha reading?
菲比
Pheebs?
是我
Hello?
菲比
Phoebe?
Phoe-Phoebe!
别闹了啦
Come on!
抱歉  我没看见你在这里
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't see you there.
菲比  你在生我的气吗
Phoebe, are you, are you mad at me, or something?
如果是  请告诉我做错了什么
'Cause if you are please, tell me what it is I did!
你不知道我也帮不了你
Well, if you don't know I can't help you.
我是不知道啊
Well, I don't know.
那我也无能为力了
Well, I can't help you.
不管是什么事  我都非常抱歉
Okay, whatever it is I'm-I'm very, very sorry. Okay?
我接受你的道歉
Apology accepted.
好的  那我们没事了
Okay. So we're, we're good?
好的
All right.
回头见
I'll uh, I'll see you later, okay?
拜  大屁股
Bye, fat ass.
够了
All right!
菲比  快说
Phoebe now come on!
你快点说  我做了什么让你这么不爽
Will you please tell me what it is I did that made you so mad at me!
我不知道  我不记得了
I don't know! I don't remember!
既然忘了  那能不能就算了
Well if you can't remember, can't we just forget about this?
不行  我生你的气  这点很确定
Oh no, I am mad at you. I know that much.
但我很抱歉骂你大屁股
But, I am sorry about the fat ass thing.
因为你的小屁屁很可爱
You actually have a very sweet little hiney.
我开得好累
Man, I'm getting pretty tired.
你随时准备接手
You're might have to take over soon.
我们才上路半小时
We've been driving for a half-hour,
而且你都没在看路
and you haven't looked at the road once.
别担心  有路走的
Don't worry, it's out there!
我想我该吃午饭了
I think I just need lunch.
是啊
Yeah.
想吃吗  我请客
You wanna eat?  My treat!
那不是罗斯的钱吗
Isn't that Ross's money?
是啊  好吧  罗斯请客
Yeah. Okay. Ross's treat!
你想吃什么
Where do you wanna eat?
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道要怎么决定
Ooh, hey, I know how we can decide!
我问你一堆问题
All right, uh, I'm gonna ask you a bunch of questions
你得很快回答
and then you have to answer real fast. Okay?
不要想事情  什么都不要想
So uh, clear your mind Clear it right out! Clear it out! Clear!
好
Okay!
你宁愿太湿还是太干
Okay, uhh, would you rather be too wet or too dry?
太干
Too dry.
你相不相信有鬼
Do you believe in ghosts, yes or no?
不相信
No!
这电影会让我翻身吗
Is this movie gonna be my big break?
不会
No!
什么
What?!
会
Yes.
你刚才说不会
Dude you said, "No!"
我也说了会
I also said, "Yes!"
你不觉得我这次会翻身吗
You don't think this is going to be a big break for me?
不觉得
No!
岂有此理
I don't believe this!
乔伊  我只是不希望你期望太高
Look Joe, I just, I just don't want to get your hopes up real high.
你在胡说什么  我是电影主角耶
What are you talking about?! I'm the lead in a movie!
他们连片酬都不给你
They're not even paying ya!
是不是真有电影觉得都很悬
This doesn't even sound like a real movie!
我不需要听这种话
Y'know what? I don't need this! Okay?
搞不懂你干嘛看贬我的翻身机会
I don't know why you're dumping all over my big break.
乔伊  我不认为这是你咸鱼翻身的机会
Joe, I don't think this is going to be your big break.
所以你才来这趟吗
Is that why you're on this trip, huh?
让我觉得自己是窝囊废
Make me feel like a loser?
如果是这样  那我宁愿自己去
'Cause if it is, I'll tell ya, I-I-I'd rather be alone.
你不要我陪你去
Oh, you don't want me on the trip?
你这样不要也罢
Not if you're gonna be like this!
那好吧
All right, I'll tell ya what,
下次你再问这种问题  我骗你就是了
the next time you ask me a question like that I'll lie.
对  我不要你一起去
Yeah! I don't want you on the trip!
好  无所谓
All right, fine! Fine!
你停车  我马上走
Why don't you pull over? I'll get out right now!
好啊
Fine!
滚吧
Get out!
在桥上不能随便停车
You're not actually supposed to stop on the bridge.
-滚啦  -好啦
- Get out!! - All right.
等等  桥上没有人行道
Wait! Wait, there's no sidewalk!
我一定会死在这里
Yeah, I'm gonna die here.
你生我的气是因为我发胶有怪味
Okay, are you mad at me because my hair gel smells?
不是
No.
你生我的气是因为我说你写字像小孩
Are you angry at me because I said your handwriting is childlike?
不是  这样才特别啊
No that made me feel precious.
我知道了
Oh, I know!
因为他老爱纠正别人的语法
Umm, is it because he's always correcting people's grammar?
什么要用"谁"的宾格啦  有时候就是"谁"啦
Whom! Whom! Sometimes it's who!
是吗  有时候是
Yeah? Sometimes it's...
是不是你玩棋盘游戏赢了他
Oh, did you beat him at a board game?
他开始居于劣势就会变得孩子气
He turns into such a baby when he starts to lose.
好  我孩子气
Okay, I'm the baby.
住手
Eh! Stop it!
钱德勒  你怎么会在这里
Chandler! What are you doing here?
乔伊在华盛顿大桥上把我赶下车
Joey kicked me out of the car on the George Washington bridge!
为什么
Why?!
不知道  他突然发飙
I don't know! He went crazy!
我们在玩那个快问
Y'know, we were playing that game where you-you ask a question
快答的游戏
and you answer it really fast.
没有我在场监督绝对不能玩那个游戏
That game should not be played without my supervision.
我不知道他干嘛气成那样
Well, I don't know what mad him so mad,
我只是说
y'know? All I said was that uh,
我不觉得这次是他翻身的机会
I didn't think this wasn't gonna be his big break,
这部电影帮不了他
that this movie wasn't going to do anything for him,
是不是真有电影觉得都很悬
and that uh, y'know it didn't sound like a real movie--
好吧  他该把我推下桥才对
Okay, he should've pushed me off of the bridge.
你袋子里是什么
What's in the bag?
我猜想你们大家也会对我不爽
Oh, I figured you guys would all be mad at me.
所以我在路边捡了些礼物
So I got you some gifts that I found on the side of the road.
谁要一条腿的泰迪熊
Who wants the teddy bear with one leg?
我要
I do!
好的
Okay.
差十万八千里
Not even close.
好啦  你帮我  我没办法
Okay, then y'know what? Help me! I need help! I can't do this!
来  我帮你
Okay! All right! Come on let's do it!
坐下
Sit down.
好
All right.
头往后仰
Put your head back.
好的
Yes! All right. Okay.
把眼睛张开
Now, open your eyes.
张开了
Okay, they are.
我举了几根手指头
How many fingers am I holding up?
四根
Four.
天啊  我心里想的也是四
Oh my God, I was thinking four.
-真的  -是的
- Really?! - Yes!
这样吧  我们先来彩排一次
All right, y'know what? Why don't we start with a practice run? Okay?
-好  -不滴眼药水
- Okay! - No drops!
太好了
Great!
数到三  一  二  三
On three, 1...2...3!
你害我抱枕都湿了
Now my pillow's all wet!
你自己说是彩排的
Well, well, you said it was practice!
那你干嘛动
Then why did you move?!
因为我知道你在骗我
Because I knew you were lying!
好吧  过来
All right, come here!
你干嘛  莫妮卡  住手
What are you doing? Monica!! Stop it!!
天啊  住手
Oh my God! Stop it!
我要...  我要...  转过来
I am going... I'm going--Turn it over!
我要把眼药水滴进你眼睛
I'm... I am going to get these drops in your eyes.
天啊  你蛮力真大
Oh my God! You really are freakishly strong!
莫妮卡  住手
Monica! Stop it!
可恶  滴完了
Damn! It's empty!
如果现在乔伊和钱德勒走进来
Wow, y'know if Joey and Chandler walked in right now,
我们就发了
we could make a fortune!
一定是钱德勒  乔伊  或是罗斯
Ooh that is definitely Chandler, Joey, or Ross.
或是瑞秋
Or-or Rachel!
喂
Hello?
是乔伊
It's Joey.
真高兴你打来  钱德勒都说了
I'm so glad you called! Chandler told me what happened.
他很难过
Y'know he's really upset about it.
等他知道他毛衣背心的下场
Not as upset as he's gonna be
他一定会更难过
when he finds out what I did with his sweater vests!
你把他的毛衣背心怎么了
What did you do to his sweater vests?
这么说吧  在俄亥俄州有一伙打扮亮丽的狗
Let's just say there's a well-dressed pack of dogs in Ohio.
莫妮卡  菲比在吗
Hey Monica listen is-is Phoebe there?
我有车子的事要问她
I gotta ask her something about the car.
她在  你等等
Yeah, she's here. Hold on a second.
好啊  哥们
Hey, dude!
菲比  有个木盒
Hey Pheebs! Listen, this wooden box
不停地从座位底下滑出来  装的什么
keeps sliding out from under the seat. What-what is it?
那是我外婆
Oh that's my grandma.
乔伊  谢谢你  她玩得很开心
And thanks Joey she's having a really great time.
是乔伊吗  我要跟他说
Is that Joey? Is that Joey? Let me talk to him! I wanna talk to him!
乔伊  钱德勒在这里  他想...
Okay Joey? Chandler's here, he was wondering...
我想他硬币正好用完了
Okay, I guess he ran out of change.
他连话都不想跟我说
Y'know, he won't even talk to me.
这样我要怎么跟他道歉
How am I going to apologize to him if he won't even talk to me?
或许你应该寄点东西给他
Well, maybe you should send him something.
等他到了赌城  就知道你想表达歉意了
So that when he gets to Las Vegas he'll know that you're sorry.
好主意  上哪儿找黄片篮呢
That's a good idea. I wonder where I could get a basket of porn...
不要  不要用黄片道歉啦
No, don't-don't say I'm sorry with porn!
是吗
Really?
你应该寄一条烟过去
Y'know what you should send him? A cartoon of cigarettes.
他可以用来换取保护
'Cause that why he could trade it for protection.
错了  监狱里才是这样
No. That's prison.
菲比  我知道要怎么找出原因
Okay Pheebs, I know how we're going to figure this out.
好的  什么都不要想
Okay, clear your mind
想到什么就直接回答  好了吗
and answer the first thing that comes into your head. Okay?
你更喜欢什么  植物还是动物
What do you like better flora or fauna?
动物
Fauna.
你想当谁  西蒙还是葛芬柯(二人演唱组合)
Who would you rather be Simon or Garfunkle?
葛芬柯
Garfunkle.
你为何生我的气
Why are you mad at me?
因为你说我很无趣
You said I was boring--Ohh!
我何时说过你无趣了
When did I say you were boring?!
天啊  我想起来了  我们下国际象棋那次
Oh my God, I remember now! We were playing chess!
菲比  我和你从没下过国际象棋
Phoebe! You and I have never played chess!
有啦  记得冰冻湖那次吗
Oh, come on! Yes, remember that time on the frozen lake?
我们下国际象棋  你说我很无趣
We were playing chess, you said I was boring,
然后你脱下面具  变成了卡梅隆·迪亚兹
and then you took off your energy mask and you were Cameron Diaz!
好吧  这有可能是梦境
Okay, there's a chance this may have been a dream.
史丹利  你的主角来了  咱们开工吧
Stanley! Hey-hey! You're leading man is here! Let's get to work.
计划有些改变  我们停拍了
Umm, slight change of plans. We've shut down.
什么  为什么
Wh-what?! Why?!
资金问题  我们没钱
It's a money thing, we don't have any.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding right?
不是
No.
什么
What?!
这或许只是暂时的
It-it's probably just temporary.
我们希望能快点筹到资金
We're hoping to get some more money soon,
你先撑一下
so if could just uh, hang out.
撑一下  要撑多久
Uh, hang out?! How long?
不知道  一两个星期吧
I don't know. A week? Maybe two?
资金会出现的
The money will turn up!
大家都爱投资拍电影
People will always wanna invest in movies!
你该不会是有钱人吧
Hey, you're not rich are ya?
我不是
No!
问一下也无妨
Eh, worth a shot.
乔伊  让我知道你在哪儿落脚
Look Joey, let me know where you're staying, okay?
伙计  你是乔伊·崔比安尼吗
Hey pal, are you Joey Tribbiani?
我是
Yeah.
这是有人送给你的
These got left for ya.
谢了
Thanks.
恭喜你翻身了
Congratulations on your big break.
喂
Hello?
莫妮卡  我是乔伊
Hey Monica, it's Joey!
乔伊  你当了大明星还是记得我
Hey Joey! Aww, you remembered even though you're a big star!
得了吧  忘记你也要好几年
Aw, come on! It'll be years before I forget you!
乔伊  拍片现场是什么样子
Joey, what's it like on a movie set, huh?
你有自己的更衣室吗
Do you have a dressing room?
有专属的私人座椅吗
Do you have a chair with your name on it?
有啊  一切都在进行当中
Uh, well yeah-yeah, I've got all of that going on.
你一定要跟钱德勒说
Yeah, listen uh, I want you to make sure you tell Chandler
他完完全全看走眼了
that he couldn't have been more wrong!
莫妮卡  我得挂了  我的寿司送来了
Uh-oh! I gotta go Monica, my uh, my sushi's here!
抱歉  多谢你们等我
Sorry about that. Thanks for waitin'.
拍吧
Okay!
大家笑一个
Everybody smile!
多谢  希望你们在凯撒宫玩得愉快
Okay, thanks a lot! Enjoy your stay at Caesar's!
祝福你们"罗马"精神
We hope it's toga-rrific!
杀了我吧
Kill me. Kill me now.
瑞秋  电视指南递给我好吗
Hey Rach, can you pass me the TV Guide?
好啊
Yep!
上
Go!!
做什么  住手  天啊
What?!! Stop it! Stop it! Oh my God!
好了
Okay! Okay! Okay!
三四个小时后再见
We'll see you in about 3 to 4 hours.